<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="CPSFrameworkXMLToDOC.xsl"?>
<!--Sample XML file generated by XMLSpy v2021 rel. 3 (http://www.altova.com)-->
<cpsframework:CPSFramework xmlns:cpsframework="cpsframework" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="cpsframework ODDAspects.xsd">
	<BusinessCase>
		<description>Automated Driver System comprises of advanced driver assistance systems and vehicle guidance systems. Scenario-based approaches can be applied to achieve the defined work products for the development of automated driving functions. A scenario is a common approach to substantiate test cases for functional modules and can be used to detail the functional description of a system.  For the design and test of functional modules (federates) of a simulation-based automated vehicle, it is essential to define interfaces (RTI) for the data transmission among these modules through vehicle bus and WLAN. Modeling of co-simulation based driving environment, as well as vehicle and traffic dynamics, is required to ensure numerical robustness, safety, reliability, security, and usability of the test scenarios.</description>
		<identifier>2020</identifier>
		<name>Scenario-based safety verification and validation of Autonomous Driving Systems</name>
		<technicalId>String</technicalId>
		<Aspects>
			<boundaries>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns related to demarcations of topological, geolocation, zones, construction locations, geofence specifications, weather restrictions, jurisdictions, Sensing/Actuation Operating Ranges, etc.
					</description>
				</Property>
			</boundaries>
			<business>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about operational constraints, traffic/right-of-way rules, infrastructure standards, vehicle type and classification.cost, etc.
					</description>
				</Property>
			</business>
			<communication>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about function including communication among on and off-vehicle, infrastrucutre Connectivity e.g. V2V and V2I communications, vehicle bus, Wireless Links etc.
					</description>
				</Property>
			</communication>
			<composition>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns related to the ability to compute selected properties of a component assembly(traffic management systems, cross-infrastructure integration) from the properties of its components.
					</description>
				</Property>
			</composition>
			<data>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about data interoperability including fusion. metadata, type and identity etc. of Operational Data such as real-time traffic/historical traffic patterns data, V2V and V2I communication and connectivity etc.
				</description>
				</Property>
			</data>
			<functional>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about function including transportaion infrustructure, road type and condition, Obstacle type and location(sensing), environmental condition, vehicle hazard status etc.
					</description>
				</Property>
			</functional>
			<human>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about human interaction with vehicle as part of CPS, including fallback driver presence/receptivity, pedestrian/biker/animal presence, vehicle owner rules, passenger presence etc.
				</description>
				</Property>
			</human>
			<lifecylce>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about the lifecycle of CPS including vehicle component lifetime limits, infrastructure lifetime limits, vehicle component/infrastructure wear status, Vehicle Reflash/FOTA, durability etc.
				</description>
				</Property>
			</lifecylce>
			<timing>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about time and frequency, including the generation and transport of time and frequency signals, timestamping, managing latency, signal-loss ride-through limits, timed maneuver limits, V2V and V2I synchronization, etc.
				</description>
				</Property>
			</timing>
			<trustworthiness>
				<Property>
					<description>
					Concerns about trustworthiness of CPS including security, privacy, safety, reliability, resilience, Critical function redundancy, DDT Fallback, MRC capability/competence etc.
				</description>
				</Property>
			</trustworthiness>
		</Aspects>
		<Domain>
			<name>Automated Driving System (ADS)</name>
			<technicalId>String</technicalId>
		</Domain>
	</BusinessCase>
</cpsframework:CPSFramework>